One of my first questions that I was very keen to ask, I mean, were you at the encampments?
I haven't had the Cambridge one, but other ones.
Other ones, okay. And can I ask you what your view is of the events of October the 7th?
What do you think happened on October the 7th in Israel?
Well, obviously the camps haven't started because of October the 7th specifically.
They're starting, I mean, this week in loads of encampments up and down the country.
They've been like celebrating and having to like memorise the fact that this week commemorates the Nakba,
which took place 76 years ago, which means catastrophe, which is a massive symbol of what Israel has been doing for the last 76 years.
This isn't about October the 7th. And to start with that is just entirely disingenuous.
I think on your part, I really want to say that I think it's great, actually, that you went to that camp today
and tried to talk to those students and you kind of embarrassed yourself, I would say, whilst doing that
because it was a reminder for me and I'm sure for other people watching that actually the Palestine movement brought you down
and the Palestine movement has the potential to bring down lots of other Tory ministers and the whole Tory government
and not just the Tory government.
I would say any government and any mainstream political party that is backing what Israel is doing right now,
which is a genocide and lots of people are protesting, bringing down the government.
Now quite often you'll see that they don't seem particularly intent on showing their faces,
I don't know if you might be able to engage with people.
Hello, just wondering if you'd like to have any kind of discussion at all with Suella today?
Hi, I'm Suella. I'm keen to find out your views and what you're protesting about.
Nothing at all? No?
Interested in why you're covering your faces?
Is it a Covid or a health measure? No comment?
Can I just ask, are you students out of the university or just from around the area? Nothing? No?
Fine. OK. Interesting.
What were you expecting? Did you think that maybe people might engage a little bit with you?
Well, these are supposed to be some of the brightest and the best students in the land
and taught in the art of articulating their views and expressing arguments in a coherent way
and I'm interested in hearing their arguments.
Yeah? Anyone?
Engaging and listening.
What would be your main question to some of the individuals?
I'm really keen to hear what your message is to Israel.
Interested to hear your message to Hamas?
No comment.
Do you think the hostages should be released now?
No?
Is that alright? We'll keep walking.
Not very conversant today.
I don't know if you would like to have a quick chat with us, sir?
At all? Should I?
Hi there.
Go on.
Very nice. I'm Suella.
Can I ask you what your message is to Israel?
Yep.
Right?
Can I ask you what your message is to Hamas?
Silence.
Guys, anyone willing to just explain a couple of bits and bobs?
What you guys are doing here?
Why it's so important to you?
What the demands are or anything?
No?
Vegan and nut fruit needed.
Vegan and nut free food...
Oh, that's what it says.
...is needed.
Right, well there we go.
Morning everybody.
Hi, I'm Suella Braverman, MP.
Here to inquire about what you're protesting about
and give you an opportunity to send your message onto national television.
No?
No.
Okay, alright.
Well, it's fascinating, really, because I thought that maybe they would give some form of response or reaction.
Yeah.
I thought they'd have a line.
Where'd they make sense of doom?
постав me your voicehole?
No.
Yeah.
That we're ongoing.
After all, a massive change.